--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
w
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
ww
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.H
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HD
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDc
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDcm
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDcmc
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDcmct
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDcmct.
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDcmct.c
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDcmct.co
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: realyinxu
www.HDcmct.com
招募Q号:76846146
this is great.
地方真好!
There's got to be 7 or 8 feet up there.
上面起码有七、八英尺高…
And 80 years of dust.
和八十年的灰尘
Look at all this height.
这样的高度…
With our bedroom upstairs we'd have all this space.
楼上做睡房  下面便有空间
For what?  Just space.
要空间做什么?  就这样空着
1 ...
2...
3!
And 4?
接下来4?
And 5?
然后5
Watch it. Watch it.
小心!
God   this place is huge.
这儿真大
It's beautiful.
真美
You guys it's absolutely incredible.  Incredible.
直难以置信  的确
A little paint you could
稍加粉饰可以
sell this tomorrow and double your money.
双倍价钱出售
Carl   you're obsessed.  A little bit.
你财迷心窍了  有点呢
Whoa   look!
看!
Hey   it's an Indian head penny.
这是古老钱币!
1 898.
1898年
It's a good omen.
这是吉祥之兆
You're the good omen.
你就是吉祥之兆
it's so great.
这太好了!
I had Rose move your 3:00 to 4:00.
我叫了露丝把会议推迟至四时
Gary Allen called late yesterday.
亚伦昨天来电话
He has to see you about the final painting bids for the loft.
他想承接粉饰工程
3:00 is the only time he can make it.
只可以在三时跟你谈谈
Sam?
森!
I'm sorry.
对不起
Relax. This isn't brain surgery you're going into.
别紧张  又不是做脑部手术
Pitching these Japanese guys makes me so nervous.
我很紧张  要跟日本人谈生意
Sam...you're going to be great   OK?
你应付得来的
What am I supposed to say?
我可以说什么?
I can't tell them my Swedish pompom girl joke   you know.
又不可以跟他们说黄色笑话
Those are great. Where'd you get those?
这很好  在哪儿买的?
Nice   huh? Molly.
慕莉送的
What do you think? Are they me?
适合我吗?
Man   look at that. A Testarossa.
那部车真了不起
Whoa.Pay off your Mustang first.
别妄想  你的车还未供完
How are you feeling?What did the doctor say?
你怎样?医生怎样说?
He said it was contagious  that it was really...
他说是传染病  别吓我
He said I shouldn't be coming in today.
他说我今天不该上班
What about the rash?   The rash?
那皮肤疹怎样?     皮肤疹?
Mmhmm.The rash is also incredibly contagious.
也会传染别人
He said they've both been spreading.  No.
他说两种病都在扩散  不!
On your genitals again?
又在下体出现?
Yeah.Yeah   right on the genitals.
对  在下体
Basically everywhere.He said that I shouldn't touch anyone.
全身都是  他叫我别碰其他人
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
对不起
You're sick.  I know.
你变态的      我知道
Morning   Paul.  Morning   Carl   Sam.
保罗  早   你们早
Morning   Mr. Wheat.
韦先生  早
Morning   Susan. You're looking good.
苏珊  你容光焕发
Sam?  yeah   yeah   yeah.
森  是…
Here it is.
给
Thanks.
谢了
Morning   Sam.  Morning. Listen
森  早      早  露丝
the Kobiashi people   They're already here.
那些日本人…      已经来了
They're early.  I know.
他们早到了      我知道
Come here.
过来吧
Andy Dillon called
狄伦曾来电…
How long have they been  About 10 minutes.
他们来了多久?      十分钟左右
Andy Dillon called and says he needs
狄伦要我们在十时前…
$900  000 transferred to Albany by 1 0:00.
把九十万过户到阿尔班尼
By 1 0:00?  Yes.
十时前?      是的
Carl?
卡尔
Bill hold on
彪  请稍等
Dillon needs 900  000 in Albany by 1 0:00.
狄伦在十时前要九十万
Can you transfer it to his payroll account?
你可否把钱转到他的户口?
OK.I'll need your Mac code.
可以  但你要给我密码
Discretion   right?
别泄露  知道吗?      记下了
Got it.You bet. I'll do it right now.  thanks
当然了  我马上去办      谢谢
Bill   I'll call you back.
彪  我再打电话给你
OK   OK   that's fine. That's fine.That's fine!
好…很好
Aw   man   it's too far out.
太远了
Can you get this   man?
拿得到吗?
Where are you guys from  the New York City Ballet?
你们是什么人?芭蕾舞团团员?
Almost.
差一点
Saved your life!
救了你的命!
You shit.You scared me to death.
你吓死我了
Why'd you do that?
为什么这样做?
It's better than seeing this gorgeous body
总比看见你
splattered all over the place.
粉身碎骨好
Look out.
小心
Sam? Molly? You guys home?
森、慕莉  你们在吗?
Did you invite Carl?
你叫他来的吗?
Slave labor.
他来当苦工
Carl? What?
卡尔!      什么?
Hurry. Help.my God.
赶快帮手!      天啊!
Grab the bottom.
抓住底部
Want this down here?
放在哪儿?
Right here?
放在这儿?
Watch your toes.
小心你的脚趾
Where do you want this?Uh   in the bedroom.
想放在哪里?      睡房
God   this place looks great.
这地方很好!
Yeah.You like it   huh?
你也喜欢?
Like is hardly the word.
何止喜欢
I didn't know it would be this beautiful.
我没想到会这样好
Molly   what about her?
怎样处置它?
Leave her there until we get the rest in.
暂时把它放在那儿
What are these?
这是什么?
let me show you.
我给你看
Help me lift this up.Here?
帮我拿起它      这儿吗?
Wow.What do you think?
我刚完成  怎样?
It's fantastic. I love it.
很了不起
Sam   what's this chair doing here?
要这椅子来干嘛?
What do you mean? I love that chair.
什么意思?我很喜欢椅子
I know   but we discussed this...
我知道  但我们说好了…
I've had it forever.
这椅子一直陪着我
When I watch TV   I sit in it.
我要坐在上面看电视
This chair is ugly.
这椅子很难看
So?And it doesn't go with anything.
跟其他东西不合衬
It goes with me.
它跟我合衬
You're right. It does.
你说得对
We'll paint it.We'll what?
要涂上颜色      什么?
Are you OK?Mmhmm. I'm fine.
你没事吧?      没事
What's the matter?Nothing.
有什么事吗?      没有
You worried about the promotion?No   not really.
担心升职的事吗?      不
Then what?Is it moving in together?No.
为同居的事烦脑?      不
I don't know. It's...a lot of things.
我不晓得  很复杂
I just don't want the bubble to burst.
怕好梦成泡影
Seems like   uh...
这就像…
whenever anything good in my life happens
我每次遇上好的事
I'm just afraid I'm going to lose it.
都怕会失去
I love you.
我爱你
I really love you.
真的爱你
Ditto.
我也是
The pilot first reported trouble
机尾的二号引擎发生爆炸
when the number two engine blew
机上载满了乘客
Jesus   another one?
又一宗飞机失事
don't watch that.
别看了
I should cancel my L. A. trip.These things always happen in threes.
我该取消行程  祸事总接二连三
Sam   get serious.Besides   you lead a charmed life.
你太认真了  你一向吉星高照
yeah? So did they.
他们也是
It's amazing.
真可怕
Just like that.Blackout.
眼前一黑  什么都完了
My love
My darling
I've hungered for...
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
I couldn't sleep.
我睡不着
I must have passed out.
我定是睡着了
What time is it?It's 2 a.m.
现在什么时候?      凌晨两点
Goes by
So slowly
Any time
Can do so much
Are you
Still mine
no.I hope it wasn't a masterpiece.
希望这不是你的杰作
It's not now.
现在不是了
Can I help?  Yeah.
我可以帮你吗?      可以
Put your hands here and get them wet.
把手放在这儿
Just let the clay slide between your fingers.
让粘土在指间流过
God speed your love
To me
Lonely rivers Flow
To the sea
To the open arms
Of the sea
Yeah
Lonely rivers sigh
Wait for me
I'll be coming home
Oh
My love
My darling
I've hungered
Hungered for your touch
A long
Lonely time
And time
Goes by
So slowly
Any time
Can do so much
Are you
Still mine
I need
Your love
I
I need your love
God speed your love
To me
no.
我不知道
What's the matter?
什么事?
A glitch. What's up?
小问题  有什么事?
The Greenberg and White accounts I can't get in.
我入不到一些户口
The Mac code isn't working.
密码无效
I changed it.Why?
我改了      为什么?
Nothing. I want to nose around a bit.
只是想查查这些户口
Is something wrong?
有何不妥?
Can you keep a secret?
你可以保守秘密吗?
Yeah   sure.What's up?
当然  什么事?
There's too much money in these accounts.
这些户口有太多存款
Too much money? That's impossible.
过多?这不可能的
Sam
森
this is going to take you hours.Let me do this.
这会花你很多时间  让我做吧
It's already taken me hours.
我已花了很多时间
Let me figure it out.
让我替你完成它
No   that's OK.It's like a vendetta now.
不  现在这就像我的世仇一样
Thanks   though. I appreciate it.
谢谢你
OK.If you start to go blind   give a shout.
倦了的话就大声叫我
OK. Adios.
好  再见
Listen   what are you and Moll doing tonight?
你和慕莉今晚有什么节目?
We're going to the theater to see Macbeth.
我们去看莎士比亚的戏剧
She likes the guys in tights.
她喜欢男人穿贴身裤
You want to go?
你想去吗?
No   thanks.I want a full report   though.
不  但你之后要向我汇报
Later.Yeah.
再见      再见
Well   I loved it.I was spellbound the whole time.
他们的演出很精彩
I could tell.So could everyone else with that resonating snore of yours.
是  但你整晚在打鼾
Did I tell you what Melissa said?
我有跟你提过美施的话吗?
Yeah   about six times.
提了六次左右
It wasn't six times.
才没有
Quit being so blase about this.
别这么冷淡
This is really important.
这很重大
I'll have two pieces in her gallery.
我有两件作品在画廊展览
The New York Times reviews her gallery all the time.
时代周刊经常报导那画廊
Molly   The New York Times is just some frustrated little critic
时代周刊的人只是失意的评论家
with pimples on his ass who flunked art school.
一些被美术学校退学的人
Who cares what they think?
谁在乎他们想什么?
About eight million readers   that's who.
杂志有八百万读者
Nah   they're just reading the sports page.
他们只看体育版
Your work is really beautiful.It really is.
你的作品很漂亮
Thanks.It shouldn't matter
谢谢 我觉得
what anyone else thinks just what I think.
其他人怎么想并不重要
I want to marry you   Sam.  What?
森  我想跟你结婚      什么?
What?  Yep.
什么?  没错
I've been thinking about it.
我一直在想
I've been thinking about it a lot
想了很多
and I think we should just do it.
我们该结婚
You're serious.  Yeah.
你认真的吗?      是的
What's that look for?
为什么这个样子?
You never wanted to talk about it.
你从来不想提的
Do you love me   Sam?
你爱我吗?
Well   what do you think?
你认为呢?
Why don't you ever say it?
为什么不说出来?
What do you mean? I say it all the time.
我常说的
No   you say ""ditto  ""and that's not the same.
不  你只说 我也是  这不一样
People say I love you all the time  and it doesn't mean anything.
常把我爱你挂在嘴边并不意味着什么
You know   sometimes you need to hear it.
人有时需要听一听
I need to hear it.
我需要听你说
Let's go.
走吧
What should we do?   Let me handle it.
该怎么办?      我来应付
What do you want?
你想怎样?
Your wallet give it to me!
给我钱包
Sam   just give it to him.
给他吧
OK   just take the money. Just leave
把钱拿去好了
No   Sam
森
You son of a bitch!
混蛋!
Sam   don't!
森  不!
Somebody help us!
救命!
Somebody!Somebody help us!
Sam   just let...
森  算吧
Sam   stop it.Stop it   Sam!
森  停手吧
Molly?
慕莉
Molly   he got
慕莉  你要…
Sam...
森
Baby   hold on.You're going to be OK.
支撑下去  没事的
Somebody?Somebody?
来人!
Somebody help us!
救命!
my God.Sam. come on.Hold on   baby.
天啊  坚持住  森 坚持住
Someone's going to come.
快有人来的了
You're going to be OK.
会没事的
Somebody!Somebody help me!
救命!
Please   anybody!
来人!
Help me. Please help me.
救我
Take it easy   all right?
别紧张  你没事吧?
We'll help you   OK?
我们来帮你
Molly? Molly?
慕莉…
All right. All right.
没事的
What should we do?
我们该怎么办
What's happening?
发生什么事了?
What's...
怎么
Is he breathing?
他仍有呼吸吗?
I don't know if he's breathing.
我不知道
Don't die   Sam. Hold on.
森  支撑下去
Come on   man.
撑住
All right.
好了
Here we go.
该走了
1 ...
Come on   baby.
挺住
Sam   don't you leave me.Sam   hold on!
森  别离开我  坚持住
Sam...
森…
Jesus...
上帝保佑
Miss Jensen   if you'll just step this way   please.
请到这边来
So   what happened to you?   What?
你遇上什么事?      什么?
You're new   huh? I could tell.
你新来的?我看得出
Are you talking to me?
你跟我讲话?
Relax. It ain't like before.It's a whole new ball of wax.
放松点  你从此跟以前不同了
Who are you?
你是谁?
I'm waiting for my wife.She's in the cardiac wing. She's fighting it.
我在等我老婆  她还在垂死挣扎
Shot   huh?
中枪?
That'll do it every time.
总难免一死
Poor bastard.
可怜人
You may as well get used to it.
你要适应
You could be here for a long while.
你可能要在此一段时间
Come here. I'll tell you a secret.
告诉你一个秘密
Doors ain't so bad.
门挡不到你
Zip   zap they ain't nothing.You'll see. You'll catch on.
形同虚设  你会学到的
He ain't going to make it.
他不行了
I've seen it a million times.He's a goner.
我见过无数次  他没救了
You see?Here they come.
看见吗?天堂之光来了
Lucky bastard.It could have been the other ones.You never know.
他幸运  地狱使者没有来勾魂
Who are
谁是…
No!
不
God help me.
救我
God...help me.
""I am sunk in the abysmal swamp where there is no foothold.
我踏进无底的深渊…
I have reached the watery depths.The flood overwhelms me.
泥足深陷  洪水把我淹没
I am wearied with calling.''
我惶恐大叫
As we say farewell to our friend Sam Wheat
我们告别好友韦森…
we are reminded of his kindness...his generosity his buoyancy of spirit.
想起他生前慈祥慷慨、为人活跃
All that we treasure
我们所珍惜的…
our loved ones  our friends  our body  our mind
爱人、朋友、躯体、思想
are but on loan to us.We must surrender them all.
全是暂借回来  终要交还
We are all travelers on the same road
我们不过是同路的过客
which leads to the same end.
走向同一个尽头
As our loved one enters eternal life
我们所爱的人已得到永生
let us remember that love   too   is eternal.
同样我们的爱也是永恒
That although we will miss him
虽然我们会怀念他
our love will light the void and dispel the darkness.
但爱会驱除黑暗
I picked up your shirts today.I don't know why.
我今天去洗衣店拿你的衫
Mr. Reynolds told me to tell you hello.
老板问候你
I broke into tears.
我忍不住流泪
It's like I think about you every minute.
我老是想着你
It's like I can still feel you.
感觉你仍在身旁
I'm here   Moll.
慕莉  我在这儿
Floyd   what's the matter   kitty?
猫咪  怎么了?
Crazy cat.
怪猫!
Sam?
森?
That's really stupid.
我真傻
I love this picture.
我喜欢这张照片
It's great.Office.
这很好…办公室的
Let me see that.
让我看看
It's   um...Sam's address book.   Right.
森的通讯录      对
Dave Brubeck. Newport   '88.Should I toss them?
88年的音乐会门票  要撕掉吗?
No.No? Molly   we hated that concert.
别  慕莉 我们讨厌那音乐会
You wanted to save those?
你要留下那些?
Rolaids?Molly   what are you doing?
胃药?留着干嘛?  慕莉  你在干嘛?
I just miss him   Carl.
我很想他
Me   too.
我也是
Carl?  Yeah?
卡尔      什么?
Wait a minute. Wait.
等等
What?Not that one.
别拿走那个
Which? I'm sorry.I didn't mean to put that on there.That's OK.
哪个?我无意拿走它  别介意
Hey   Moll   why don't you come?
你何不跟我出去?
It's like summer outside.
外面像夏天
No   I'm really not up for it.
我没有心情
Just for a walk.
来吧  你该出外走走
I don't want to.
我不想去
You can't stay in all day.
你不能整天躲在屋里
It's not healthy.
这很不健康
Carl   I can't do it!
我做不到
Molly   you're not the one who died.
死的人又不是你
I'm sorry.  Don't apologize.
对不起      不用道歉
Shit.
该死
Maybe you're right.Maybe just a short one.That a girl.
你说的对 应该出去走会儿      这才对
I'm sorry.Don't worry about it.
对不起      别介意
Molly!
慕莉?
What are you doing here?
你来干什么?
You bastard.
你这混蛋!
You son of a bitch!
混蛋!
What do you want?
你想怎样?
Molly?Molly   get out!
慕莉?到屋外去!
my God.
天啊
No   Molly! Look   no   no   please!
慕莉  别进去
Molly!Molly   he's got a gun!
他有枪
Hi   kitty. Hi.
小猫咪
You hurt her
你伤害她  我就…
Shit!
该死
Is somebody there?Hello?
有人吗?
Hello?
my God!
你怎么了?
Let go! What are you doing?
你这个疯子快放手  你做什么?
Like trains?
喜欢列车吗?
Stay out! This is mine!
滚出去  这是我的地盘
(威里卢兹)
Shit.
该死
It's me. I couldn't get it.She came home.
是我  我拿不到  她回来了
Give me a couple of days   man.I'll go back.
两天之后我会再去
Relax.I'll get it.
别紧张  我会拿到的
Get what?
拿什么?
Who are you?What do you want from us?
你是谁?想要什么?
No.You stay away from her.
不要接近她
Do you hear me?Stay away from her!
听见吗?别接近她!
(通灵顾问)
Rosa Santiago?
桑缇雅歌
Please be seated.
请坐
Our sister will be with us soon.
姐姐就快出来
Sister Oda Mae grant us the gift of your allseeing presence.
奥德美姐姐  请现身
Appear before us now.
请马上出现
Mrs. Santiago?
桑缇雅歌太太
Buenos dias.
你好
I'm Oda Mae Brown.
我是奥德美
I understand you wish to contact your husband.
你要跟亡夫接触?      是的
I believe he'll be with us today.  Thank you.
我相信他今天会出现      谢谢
But you know   Mrs. Santiago
但是你要知道桑缇雅歌太太
there's no telling about that other world
信则有  不信则无
so you've got to be a believer   Mrs. Santiago.Are you a believer?
你要相信才行  你相信吗?
Si. Si   I believe. I believe.
我相信
Then let us begin.
那么现在开始
I can't.I can't. It's too difficult.
我做不到  太困难了
I can't make contact. I don't feel his vi
看来不能跟他接触
No   wait!
我感觉不到他的…且慢!
I'm feeling something.Did he know someone by the name of Anna?
他认识叫安娜的人吗?
Consuelo?
康苏鲁?
Lucita?
鲁丝达?
Julietta?Josefina? Linda?
茱莉叶达?祖瑟芬…
Maria?     I Si! His mama!She is Maria!
玛利亚?      他妈妈叫玛利亚
Yes! Praise God   I knew he was with his mama.
谢天谢地  他跟妈一起
my God.
天啊!
It's too difficult. It's two of them.
太困难了  他俩在一起
I'm not sure I can do that.It's so trying.
我不确定我能否做到  太难了
I pay more. How much?
我可以多付些钱
How much?   $20.
要多少?      二十块
Way to go. Milk her for every penny.
把她的钱都骗光吧
Huh. Yes   I...I believe we can start again.
我们从头再来吧
Thank you   Jesus.  Thank you   Jesus.
感谢主
Welcome   Mrs. Santiago.You're fortunate today.
你今天真好运
The spirits are churning.
亡魂来了
My husband?
我丈夫?
Have mercy!
很幸运
yeah? Where?
是吗?在哪儿?
Julio?    Yes!
朱里奥?   是的
I feel his vibration.
我感觉他的振动
I see him!
我看到他
How is he? How does he look?
他是怎样子?
he's a handsome man.  Handsome?
很英俊      英俊?
Mrs. Santiago   in Our Father's kingdom  we're all handsome.
在天国的人都很英俊
Julio.
朱里奥!
Julio's coming towards us.I see him! He's coming!
朱里奥正走过来
He's there!
就在那儿
He's dressed in a black suit.
他穿着黑色衣服
Black suit?
黑色衣服?
It could be blue.
可能是蓝色的
What a crock of shit.
真是装神弄鬼!
Who is that?
谁?
Julio? Julio?
朱里奥?
Julio! Where are you?
你在哪儿?
Did you hear it?
你听到吗?
Damn! Where are you?
你在哪儿?
Julio?
朱里奥
Who are you?Whoa!
你是谁?
You can hear me?
你听到我的话吗?
Don't you hear him?
你没听到他说话?
I don't believe this.Hey   you   my name's Sam Wheat.
真难以置信  我叫韦森
Can you hear me? Sam Wheat. Say my name.
你听到吗?把我的名字说出来
Leave me alone!
别缠着我
Say it! Sam Wheat!
叫我的名字  韦森
Talk to me   Oda Mae. Say something!
奥德美  说些话吧
Sam Wheat!
韦森
Jesus.
天啊!
Sam Wheat?  Sam Wheat?
韦森?
I swear   no more cheating.
我发誓不再骗人
I'll do anything. I'll do penance but make that guy go away!
我答应会赎罪  叫他走吧
No way.
妄想
It's OK.
没事的…
Yeah   you're all right.
你没事的
My mother and my mother's mother both had the gift.
我妈和外婆都会通灵
They always said I had it   but I never did.I never had it.
但我一直不会
They told me all about it.
她们教晓我通灵之道
But now that I got it   I don't think I want it.
现在我能了  但我不想通灵
Go away. Find somebody else.
你另找他人吧
Somebody else? You're out of your mind.
另找他人?你疯的吗?
I'm getting there fast.
我快疯了
She hit her head harder than we think.
她的头撞得很伤
She was talking to nobody before she hit her head.
她撞头前已这样自言自语
Sister can do that.
我知道  但姐姐可以这样做
Where exactly are you?
你到底在哪儿?
Standing right beside you.
站在你身旁
you're standing right beside me?
站在我身旁?
Well   honey   we're right here.
我们都在这儿
Are you white?  What?
你是白人?      什么?
White?
白人?
You're white   aren't you?
你是白人吧?
Know what I think?I'll call the doctor right now.
知道我想什么吗?      快找医生
I knew it. A white guy. Why me?
早知道你是白人  为何缠着我?
Listen   damn it. You're going to help me.
我要你帮忙
There's a woman named Molly Jensen.She's in terrible danger.
有个叫慕莉的女人现在很危险
The man who killed me
杀死我的人
broke into our apartment and he's going to go back.
会潜入我们的寓所
You've got to warn her.
你要警告她
What makes you think she'll listen to me?
你以为她会听我的话吗?
It's just a phone call.
只是打个电话
Look...
听着
you're all I've got.
你只可以靠你
Now   I'm not leaving until you help me.
你不帮我  我就不走
I don't care how long it takes  'cause I can talk forever.
不管多久  我可以不停说话
Hello?Uh   hi. Is this Molly Jensen?
你是慕莉吗?
Yes.My name's Oda Mae Brown.I'm a spiritual reader and advisor.
我是奥德美  是个通灵顾问
A friend of yours gave me a message for you.
你朋友有话要传给你
I know this sounds crazy   but it's notYou got to believe me.
我知道这有点怪  但你要相信我
Just don't be afraid.
别害怕
Who is this?
谁?
I got a message from Sam.
森有口信给你
What?
什么?
Sam Wheat? He asked me to call.
是韦森要我打电话给你
I told you.
我早说过
Go there.
你要亲自去一次
Forget it. I'm not going anywhere.I don't care what you do.
我不会去的  不管你怎样
Second verse Same as the first
第二节跟首节一样
I'm 'Enery the Eighth I am
(我是亨利八世)
I got married to the widow next door
(我会娶隔邻的寡妇)
She's been married seven times before
(她结过七次婚)
And every one was an 'Enery Wouldn't have a Willy or a Sam
(每个都是亨利  不是别人)
No   sir I'm her eighth old man I'm 'Enery
(我是她第八任丈夫)
'Enery the Eighth I am   I am
(亨利八世…)
Second verse Same as the first
第二节跟首节一样
I'm 'Enery the Eighth I am
(我是亨利八世)
I got married to the widow next door
(我娶了隔邻的寡妇)
All right! All right! Stop singing!I'll go anywhere you want to
好了  别再唱  我去好了
just don't sing anymore.
求你别再唱
I can't believe this.I can't believe I'm doing this.
想不到我会这样做
What am I doing down here?I never come downtown. I hate downtown.
我最讨厌来闹市
She's probably not even there.
她可能不在家
Where are you?
你在哪儿?
Which building is it?
是哪幢房子?
Uh   push 3.
按
See? Nobody's there.She's there. Just wait.
没人在家      她在的  等一会
I did everything I said I'd do.
我答应过你的都做了
I pressed the button.
只是她不在家  我要走了
She's not there. I'm going.
多等一会      对不起
99 bottles of beer on the wall
(九十九瓶啤酒…)
99 bottles of beer
(拿一瓶  到处传…)
Take one down Pass it aroundDon't sing   all right?
好了  别唱了
Shh! She can't hear you.
她听不到你的话
Hi   I'm Oda Mae.I called you about your friend Sam Wheat?
我是奥德美  曾跟你谈及韦森
I told you.
我早说过
Molly! Molly Jensen.I know you're up there. I know you hear me.
慕莉  你在屋里  听到我的话
I'm down here. Sam wants to talk to you.This is for real.
森有话要跟你说  是真的
Remember the starfish in Montego Bay?
你还记得蒙特哥湾的海星吗?
How would I know that if he wasn't here?
他不跟我说  我怎晓得?
Hey   Molly   I know about the green underwear that
你还在绿色内衣
you wrote your name on.
写上自己的名字
I'd never get over that   I tell you that.
这个我永不会忘记
I know about the picture in Reno.
你在雷诺城跟他拍过照
Ask her about the sweater she knitted in the closet that's too big.
告诉她衣橱里那件她织的毛衣太大了
He asked me to remind you of the sweater in the closet
他告诉我说衣柜里
that you knitted that's too big.
你编织的毛衣太大了
Four sizes.
大了四个码
Hey   you hear me talking to you?
你听到我的话吗?
I hear you.   Shut up. Nobody's talking to you.
我听到了      我不是跟你说
Ever hear of a phone?  Want to kiss my butt?
你不晓得用电话吗?      去你的
I'm not staying down here all day.Thank God.
我不会在这里久留      谢天谢地
Aw   man   shut up.
闭嘴
Molly!
慕莉
I'm going to count to 3  and I'm out of here.
我数三声之后就走
1    2   3.
一二三
No   Oda   wait.No.
等等      不
It's Molly.
是慕莉
Molly?
慕莉?
I'm Oda Mae Brown.
我是奥德美
I don't know you or Sam
我不认识你  也不认识森
but let me tell you what he did.
他却害得我好苦
He kept me up all night singing I'm Henry The Eighth   I Am.
整晚在唱我是亨利八世
That's how he got me to go out with him.
他也是这样叫我出去
Look   I'm sorry.I just I just don't believe
对不起  我…
in this life after death stuff.
我不相信鬼魂之说
Well   tell her she's wrong.
说她错了
He says you're wrong.
他说你错了
You're talking to him right now?
你现在跟他说话?      是的
He just asked me to tell you that you're wrong.
他要我说  你错了
So where is he?
他在哪儿?
I can't see him. I can only hear him.
我看不到他  只听到他的声音
I'm right here.
我在这儿
That doesn't help   Sam.
森  没用的
I'm holding her hand.
我握着她的手
He says he's holding your hand.
他说正握着你的手
What are you doing?What do you think you're doing to me?
你到底在做什么?你想对我做什么?
If you think I'm here for my health   you're crazy.
若你以为我来寻开心  你就错了
Sam's dead   OK? He's dead.
森死了
Tell her I love her.
告诉她  我爱她
He says he loves you.
他说他爱你
Sam would never say that.
森从来不会这样说
Say ditto.
跟她说  我也是
What the hell is ditto?Ditto!
什么?我也是!
To tell you the truth  I don't know how I'm doing this.
老实说  我不知自己怎么做得到
Confidentially   nothing like this has ever happened to me before.
这种事从没在我身上发生
I mean   nothing.Now I can't turn it off.
现在却欲罢不能
Is this him? Is this you?
这是他?这是你?
Yeah.  Yeah.
是的
Huh. Cute.White   but cute.
虽然你是白人  但很帅
What I don't understand is  why did he come back?
我不明白他为何回来
I don't know.
我不知道
Why is he still here?
为什么还在?
He's stuck   that's what it is.He's in between worlds.
他是进退两难  夹在阴阳之间
You know   it happens sometimes
这种事常发生
that the spirit gets yanked out so quick
人突然死去
that the essence still feels it has work to do.
总觉有心愿未了
Would you stop rambling?
别乱说
I'm just answering her question.
我只是回答她的问题
He's got an attitude now.
他在发脾气
I don't have an attitude.Yes   you do have an attitude.
我没有      你有
We're having a little discussion.
我们正在讨论
If you didn't have a attitude
你没发脾气的话
you wouldn't have raised your voice.
就不会提高声量
God damn it   Oda Mae
该死  我没提高…      别咒骂我
Don't you god damn me.Don't you take the Lord's name in vain.
别随便咒骂我  我可受不了
Would you relax?You relax.You're the dead guy.
放松点      你放松点  你已死了
Want me to help? You apologize.
你要我帮你  就得道歉
Jesus Christ!I'm leaving.
天啊!    我走了
Nobody talks to me like that   you understand?
我走了  没人会这样跟我说话
Now   you better apologize.
你最好道歉
I'm sorry.I apologize.OK?
对不起  我道歉  好了吧?
Now   would you sit down?Please?
请你坐下
He's apologized.
他在道歉
I need you to tell Molly what I'm saying
请把我的话
but you have to tell her word for word.
原原本本告诉慕莉
word for word.Yes.
原原本本      好
He wants me to tell you what he's saying word for word.
他要我原原本本转述他的话
Molly   you're in danger.
慕莉  你有危险
You can't just blurt it out like that.
你说话不可以这样直接
And quit moving around   will you?You're making me dizzy.
别再走来走去  弄得我头都晕了
I'll just tell her in my own way.
我会用我的方式说
Molly   you in danger   girl.
慕莉  你身陷险境
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
I know the man who killed me.
我知道谁杀死我
He knows who killed him.
他知道谁杀死自己
His name's Willy Lopez. I know where he lives.
他叫威里卢兹  我知道他的地址
He's a Puerto Rican   Willy Lopez.He knows where he lives.
他叫威里卢兹  他知道他的地址
Write it down.
把它写下来      他想你写下来
You write it down.I ain't no damn secretary.
你写下来      我又不是秘书
Just do it!
照做吧
He's so testy.
他很暴躁
What is it you want me to write?
要我写什么?
It's 303 Prospect Place   apartment 4D.
光景台303号  4D室
303 Prospect Place?Yeah.
光景台303号?      对
That's my neighborhood.
在我家附近
Molly   he's got my wallet  he's got my key and he was in here.
他有我的钱包门匙  还进过我家
He's got his wallet and key and was here.
他有他的钱包门匙  还进过他家
Yesterday after your walk with Carl
你昨天跟卡尔散步回来
you talked to Floyd   took off your clothes
跟猫咪玩  跟着更衣…
All right   all right.
好了…
When you came in after your walk with Carl
你昨天跟卡尔散步回来
he saw everything.
你更衣时  尽给他看见了
Go to the police. It was a setup.
你得报警  那是个阴谋
I was murdered.
我被谋杀
He says go to the police. He was murdered.
他要你报警  说自己被谋杀
There's somebody else involved
此事还有同谋
I don not know whom  forget it...
我不知道是谁  算了吧、
I don't want no more to do with this.
我不想干了
wait
等等
where are you go? what do you mean where am i go?I'm leaving
你要去哪儿?      我要走了
I did everything I said I'd do.And don't be following me.
我答应你的都做了  别跟着我
I'm finished. I mean it.
因为我履行了承诺
a nice life. Have a nice death.Goodbye.
祝你生活愉快  祝你死后愉快
Molly   there is no one on earth besides you
慕莉  在这世界上除了你
who wants this to be true more than me
没有人比我更希望这是真的
but you got to be rational about this.
但你得理性一点
Sam is no more in this room than
森不再存在了
Look   I understand the need to hang on to him I really do
我知道你挂念他  我也是一样
but this is absurd.
但这很荒谬
I know this seems absurd   but it had to be real.
看似荒谬  却是事实
You believed some fortuneteller from Brooklyn
你怎可以相信那些
who shows up at your door?
在你窗外大喊大叫的神棍
I watched her have a conversation with him.
我亲眼看见她跟森交谈
I don't buy it   Moll   not for a minute.
我一点都不相信
What about the things she knew?
她知道的事情怎样解释?
What things?
什么事?
The photo Sam took of me on our trip to Reno.
她知道我们在雷诺城拍照
Carl   we were alone.
当时没有其他人在旁
And the green underwear that I wrote my name in.
还知道我的内衣写上了名字
She said Sam knew who killed him.
她说森知道谁是凶手
Yeah   that he was set up.
他被谋杀
This is getting deranged.We're off the deep end.
这简直离谱  别再谈这个
She had a name and an address
她有他的名字和住址
Willy Lopez.
他叫威里卢兹
303 Prospect Place   apartment 4D.
住在光景台303号4D室
This is sick.
一派胡言
Carl.
拜托!卡尔
This is really sick.
真是一派胡言
God.
天啊!
Molly   I don't understand how you could you could...
想不到你竟信以为真
swallow this crap. I mean...this guy may not even exist.
可能根本没这个人
Maybe she's just trying to use you to set someone up.
她可能利用你来陷害人
You're right.
你说得对
You're absolutely right.
说得很对
That's what I got to find out.
我要找个水落石出
What do you mean   find out?
你打算怎么办?
She said Sam wants me to go to the police.
森想我报警
Sam wants you to go to the police?
森想你报警?
Jesus   Moll. Are you out of your mind?
慕莉  你疯了吗?
What are you going to tell the police?
你打算怎么跟警察说
That some storefront psychic has been communing with the dead?
告诉他们有人能通灵吗?
Do you know what that sounds like?
你知道这听来有多荒谬?
You're talking ghosts here   for Christ's sake.
你在说这世上有鬼
I'm sorry.This stuff just really gets to me
对不起  这事令我失态
you know?It's OK if you don't believe me.
你不相信也不要紧
I'm trying to   Molly.
我设法相信
if it'll make you feel any better I'll go check this out   OK?
为了令你安心  我会调查一下
I want you to try and get some sleep.
好好睡觉吧
All right.
好的
I'll call you in the morning.OK.
我明早给你电话      好
Good night
晚安
Be careful.
小心
Carl.
卡尔
What the hell are you doing here?
你来干什么?
Who you been talking to   Willy?
你跟谁说过?
""Talking to""? What the hell do you mean?
那是什么意思?
Some woman knows all about you   everything.
有个女人知道你的一切
Where's she getting it from?
她从何得知?
I haven't said a word to anybody.
我没跟人说过
She knows your name and where you live.
她知道你的姓名、地址
A lot of women know where I live.
很多女人都知道我住在哪儿
This is not a joke.
这不是玩笑
She knows about the murder.
她知道你杀人
I want you to find this bitch whoever she is
你要把这个女人找出来
and I want you toJust get rid of her   OK?
把她灭口
I've got $4 million stuck in a god damn computer.
我有四百万元卡在电脑中
If I don't get those codes if that money is not transferred soon...
若我找不到密码  不能把钱调走
I'm...dead.We're both dead.
就会没命  我俩都没命
Why not tell them you only launder money
告诉他们你要月初才能洗黑钱
the first of the month?
你有什么问题?
What the hell is wrong with you?Is everything a joke?
说笑吗?
You killed a man.You were supposed to steal his wallet.
我叫你去偷钱包  你却杀死了他
Was that a joke? I did you a favor.That was a freebie.
我免费帮了你
Look   these are drug dealers   OK?
他们是大毒贩
Just don't blow this for me.I've risked my job. I could go to jail.
你别破坏一切 累我失业 坐牢
$80  000 of that money is mine.
当中有八万元是我的
Look   just...let me have the key to Sam's apartment.
把森的门匙给我
I'll get the address book myself   OK?
我去找通讯录
You god damn bastard!
你这混蛋!
Why?Why? You were my friend!
为什么?你是我朋友
I had a life god damn you.I had a life!
我本该有我未完的人生
Look   I don't even believe in this stuff myself.
我本来也不相信
But she was real.
但她很真
You think I'd come down here if it wasn't real?
若不是真的  我干嘛到这儿来?
You know you told me if I had any new information
你叫我有新消息就找你
that I should come.So here I am.
所以我来了
I know how this sounds.
我知道很荒谬
I hear myself saying it  and I want to cringe.
也想打消这想法
But this woman knew things she couldn't have known.
但这女人知道她不可能知道的事
Things Sam only said to me.
森只对我说的话
OK   according to this psychic lady
根据这灵媒的话
there are ghosts and spirits all over the place
到处都有鬼魂
watching us all the time?Huh?
一直监视我们
Hell   I'm never going to get undressed again.
那我不再脱衣服了
Excuse me.I got more important things to do.
对不起  我有更重要的事
The guy's name is Willy Lopez.
那人叫威里卢兹
All I'm asking you to do is check it out.
我只求你调查他
OK. Wait here.Let me see if the guy's got a record   all right?
你等等  我看他有无犯罪记录
Great.
好
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
Where's the file on Willy Lopez?   There isn't one.
卢兹的档案呢?      没有他的
He was probably some old boyfriend
可能是她
she was trying to get even with.
诬害旧男友
This psychic woman's got a record that goes back a long way.
这灵媒反有很多案底
1967 Shreveport forgery...
1967年伪造文件
selling false I.D.Served one year 1971
1971年因偷假证件而坐牢一年
Baton Rouge   arrested for fraud.
1974年因诈骗他人的钱财
Numbers racketeering   served 10 months   1974.
而服刑十个月
Look   this is impossible..
没可能的
It goes on and on
数之不尽
She knew things   private things.
她知道很多私隐
Now how could she have known all that?
她怎么会知道?
A lot of times they read the obits.
她们会留意讣闻
She just had to see the word ""banker""boom.
她只需要看报纸
Hell they even go through your...garbage
甚至搜你的垃圾
to find things they can use
找有用的资料
letters   old papers.It doesn't take much.
像信和用过的纸张  这不是真的
No.It was real.
不  这是真的
She knew about a...a sweater I knitted.
她知道我编织的毛衣
And songs we sang.Our trip to Montego Bay.
我们唱的歌以及蒙特哥湾之旅
I'm sorry.I know this is hard.
我知道这很难过
People want so much to believe.
他们哀伤 脆弱
They're grieving they're vulnerable...
什么也想相信
and they will give anything for one last moment.
愿意付出一切
Believe me.These people know what they're doing.
相信我  这些人是有企图的
I know how you must feel but you know you can press charges.
我知你很难过  但你可以控告她
No.
不
Thank you.
谢谢
God   let this be it.
天啊!成全我吧!
Yes.
好
Hello.  Eddie? It's Carl Bruner.
艾迪?      是的
What's up?
我是卡尔      怎么了?
Everything's fine.Just we're all set.
一切准备好了
Let me know what you want me to do.
你想我做什么?
Want you to transfer the money from the 12 separate accounts
把12个帐户的钱
into a single account under the name Rita Miller.
过给美拉的帐户
OK.
好
Tomorrow at five minutes before closing 3:55 p.m.
明天关门前五分钟…
transfer the full account to the First Island Bank of Nassau
再把整个帐户转入拿素银行
registry number 4869580.
4869580的帐户
Call us when it's done.
办妥之后通知我们
OK. I've got it.
知道了
Just tell Mr. Balistrari that there won't be any more problems OK?
告诉巴里塔利先生不会再有问题
Yeah. I'll do that.Thank you.
我会的了      谢谢
Good work   Carl.
做得好
Molly   why can't you hear me?I need you.
我需要你  为何你听不到我说话
Who is it?  It's Carl   Molly.
谁?      卡尔
No.Don't open it   Molly.He's a murderer.
别开门  他是个凶手
Hi.I know it's late.I'm sorry to disturb you.
抱歉这么晚还来打扰你
I've been thinking about you all day
只是我整天想着你
and I feel really lousy about what happened last night.
我觉得自己昨晚很讨厌
This supernatural thing just
那些鬼神之说  使我…
Don't worry about it. It's OK.No   it's not.
别介意      不
You needed me to hear you   and I didn't.
你想我听你说  我却没有
I wasn't there for you   and that was...that was wrong.
我没有支持你  很不对
It's just   I...
我只是…
I justI want you to know that I'm your friend.
希望你知道我是你的朋友
Thanks   Carl.
谢谢
You were never our friend.
你从不是我们的朋友
That really means a lot to me.Me   too.
这对我很重要      我也是
I brought you some Japanese apple pears.I know you like them.
我带了水果来
Thanks.That's very sweet.
谢谢  你真好
Could I come in for a second?
可以进来一会吗?
It's just been one of those days.
我不会久留  像从前一样
Maybe some coffee?
喝杯咖啡
Yeah. Come on in.
进来吧
No   Molly.
不!
You seem a little tense.Are you OK?
你神态紧张  没事吧?
No. I'm fine.It's just What can I tell you?
没事  这些日子很难熬
It's been tough.It just still hurts so much.
这事所造成的打击真不少
You lying snake.
撒谎鬼!
And on top of it   it's stuff at work.
工作上又遇上不少问题
They've given me my own accounts
他们让我自己负责帐户
which is good  but I just haven't really had time to adjust
我没有时间适应
kind of absorb everything.
消化一切
It's no big deal.
没什么大不了
Yeah.Can I have just a little more cream?
可以多给我忌廉吗?
shit.Jesus. I can't believe I did that.
天啊!我真是不小心
Are you all right?Yeah   I'm fine.
你没事吧?      没事
Let me throw that in the washer.
我拿去洗
Don't worry about it. It's OK. It's just...
别为这个粗心
You want another shirt?  No. It'll dry. It'll just take a minute.
换衣服吗?      不  很快会干
Where were you today?I thought you were going to
还以为你今天
come into the bank and sign those papers?
会到银行来签文件
I was supposed to   but I didn't have time.
我没有时间
I went to the police.
我去了警局
You did?Wow. What did you tell them?
真的?你跟他们说了什么?
What did they say?It was awful.
他们怎么看  很糟
I felt really stupid.
我觉得自己很笨
They brought out a file on this woman and
他们让我看那女人的档案
At least 10 inches thick.
起码厚达十英寸
A rip off artist   huh?
她是个骗徒?
No   Molly.
不  慕莉
You know   the sad thing...is that I believed her.
最难过的是我相信她
Molly...
慕莉
sometimes we need to believe.
有时难免会相信
Why? What's the point?
为什么?
Molly   it's not easy to face the realities of life sometimes.
面对现实不容易
You got to give yourself that.
你得放纵自己
What you've got to remember is the love that you guys felt.
记住你俩之间的爱
You got to remember how good Sam was.
记住森有多好  有多爱你
You were everything to him Molly.You were his life.
你就是他的一切  他的生命
I feel so alone.
我觉得很孤单
You're not alone.OK?
你并不孤单
You got your work. You're incredibly talented.You're young.
你有工作 有天赋  而且还年轻
You're fantastically gorgeous.
你很了不起
I don't know what's real anymore.
我再也分不出真假
I don't know what to think.
不知道该想什么
Just think about Sam.
想想森吧
Think about the time you guys had together.
想想跟他一起的时候
How wonderful that was.
怎样美妙
Yeah.Let your feelings out   Moll. It's OK.
你哭出来吧
Life turns on a dime.You know?
生命会突然转变
I mean...people think that...
人们总以为
they're there forever that there's always going to be tomorrow
自己有明天
but that's bull shit.Sam taught us that.
那是废话  森的死已告诉我们
You have to live for now.
我们活着是为了现在
For today.
为了今天
I can't.I'm sorry.  It's OK.
不可以  对不起      不要紧
III can't. It's just too soon.It's OK.
不可以  太快了      不要紧
You've been great   Carl.
你一直都很好
But I need you to leave.I understand totally.
但我觉得你该离开了     我完全明白
Please.
求求你
Could we just have dinner tomorrow night? Just talk?
明晚一起吃饭吧  只是聊聊天
Can I interest you in that?
赏面吗?
Yeah.Sure.  Great.
好      太好了
Get off my train!  No.
离开我的列车!      不
Get off!
给我滚!
Get off!Get off!
滚!
Get off!Get out of here!
快滚!离开这儿
No.Show me how you do that.I'm not leaving till you teach me.
教我你的本领  否则我不会离开
Get off!  No.
滚!      不
Get off!
快滚!
You stubborn asshole.
顽固的傢伙!
What are you doing?What the hell are you doing?
你在做什么?
What am I doing?
什么意思?
You're trying to move it with your finger.
你竟想用手指移动它
You can't push it. You're dead.
你已经死了  不能再用手指推它
It's all in your mind.
你要用意志
The problem with you is you still think you're real.
不能以为自己还是实体
You think you're wearing those clothes?
你以为自己还有穿衣服
You think you're crouched on that floor?
蹲着在地上?
Bull shit!
笨蛋!
You ain't got a body no more   son!
你已没有躯体  现在得靠这儿
It's all up here!You want to move something
想推动事物
you got to move it with your mind!
就要靠意志
You got to focus!do you understand?
你要集中意志  听到吗?
How? How do you focus?
如何集中?
I don't know how you focus.You just focus.
只要集中就好了
How did you do that?
你怎么做得到?
You got to take all your emotions all your anger
你只需要把愤怒
all your love all your hate
爱恨
and push it way down into the pit of your stomach
迫到内心深处
and let it explode like a reactor. Pow!
让它像核反应堆般爆发出来
OK.OK.
好
Don't laugh.
别笑
Way to go   kid.
就是这样
I did it.I did it.
我做到了
Way to go.
就是这样
From your gut   like I told you.
由体内激发出来
Give it time. What else have you got?
慢慢来  你时间多的是
How long have you been here?
你在这儿多久了?
Since they pushed me.
我被推落铁轨之后
Someone pushed you?Yeah   someone pushed me.
有人推你?      是的
Who?   You don't believe me?
谁?    你不相信吗?
You think I fell? You think I jumped?fuck you!
你以为我失足或自己跳下去吗?
It wasn't my time!I wasn't supposed to go!
我不该这么早就死去
I'm not supposed to be here!
不该在这儿
I'd give anything for a drag.
我很想抽一口
Just one drag.
只是一口
Are you all right?
你没事吧?
Who are you? Why are you hounding me?
你是谁?为什么缠着我?
Who sent you?
谁派你来的?
Leave me alone.
别缠着我
Leave me alone!Leave me alone!
Yes!You need to concentrate 'cause if you concentrate
你集中意志
you'll probably rouse him.
就可以叫他出来
What's his name again?Orlando.
他叫什么名字?      奥兰度
Orlando. Orlando. Is there an Orlando here?
这里有叫奥兰度的吗?
I'm here.
在此!      他在这儿
He's here.Sam.
奥德美      森
Oda Mae   IExcuse me. I'm Orlando.The line's over there.
我是奥兰度  你该排队
Where did these ghosts come from?
哪里来这么多鬼?
You can hear them   too?
你能听到他们的话吗?
I hear them in the morning and the evening.
我早上听得到
They're coming into the shower.
晚上也听得到  洗澡时也听得到
Did you tell every spook you met about me?
你做过什么?
I got spooks from Jersey coming in here.
新泽西的鬼也来找我
There's stuff going on you wouldn't believe.
想不到会发生这种事
It's amazing. You're really doing it.I know.
你真的可以通灵      我知道
Can you hurry this up?
你们快点好吗?
chill out. Chill out.
冷静一点
I need your help.There's something we need to do.
我想你多帮我一个忙
I'm not doing anything else with you   Sam.
不  我不会再帮你
You're holding on to a life that doesn't want you anymore.
你还眷恋着前生
It doesn't want you. Give up the ghost.
但它不想要你  放弃吧
Are you speaking to me?
你跟我说吗?
Does it look like it?
我像跟你说吗?
You're supposed to be concentrating   aren't you?
我跟你说时  你自会知道
You going to try it?
你该集中意志
Thank you very much.
集中你的意志吧  谢谢
Sam   are you going to get out of here?
森  你出去吧  我还有工作
Fine   then stay there.
不走是你的事
Excuse me.Excuse me.You ready now?
对不起  你准备好了吗?
Let's do it.
现在开始
I got to talk to you now.I've got a plan.
我要现在跟你说  我有个计划
All we got to do is we can...
我想到了  我们只要…
Oda Mae?
奥德美
Oda Mae.
奥德美?
Ortisha?
奥缇莎?
Orlando. Is that you?
奥兰度  是你吗?
Ortisha   where you at? I can't hardly see.
奥缇莎  你坐在哪?我看不到你
Here. ShShe's here.
她在这儿
In front of you. I'm right here.
我就在你面前
Damn   baby   what did you do to your hair?
你的头发怎么了?
Orlando   you like it?It's autumn sunrise.
喜欢吗?这是秋日晨曦型
Get out of me   you son of a bitch.
混蛋  你给我滚!
Don't you ever do that to me again.
别再这样对我!
Orlando?
奥兰度
I can barely move.
我不能动
You should know better than that.
你应该知道
Jumping into bodies wipes you out.
上身会耗尽你的气力
Everybody out.
全给我滚!
What happened to Orlando?Where's the insurance policy?
奥兰度怎么了?保险单放在哪?
Are you deaf?I said everybody out!
你聋的吗?我叫你们滚!
Everybody out!Get out! Get out!
滚出去!
Get out.Everybody get out!
滚
You the fortuneteller?
你就是那个算命婆?
Who are you?
你是谁?
That's an interesting question.
问得好
Why don't you tell me?
由你告诉我吧
Willy.
威里
Willy?
威里?
Prospect Place Willy?
光景台的威里?
Get out of here fast.
快离开这儿
Oda Mae! Sister! Sister!
奥德美
I'm all right. I'm all right.
我没事
We're in trouble   so you got to help.
我们有麻烦  你要帮帮我
What do you mean we? You're already dead.
你不明白吗?你都已经死了
These people are trying to kill me.
现在是他们想杀的是我
And they'll be back.
你说得对  他们会再来
Why don't you just find a house to haunt?
你找个房子去骚扰吧
Get some chains and rattle them or something.
制造些怪声吓人吧
I have a plan   and it will work
听我说好吗?我有个很好的计划
but get some of your fake I.D.s.
你要弄张假身分证
Forget it.
妄想
If you do this   they'll never bother you again.
完成之后再没有人会骚扰你
Scout's honor.
答应吧
All right.What do I have to do?What exactly do I have to do?
好  到底要我做什么?
You got a nice dress?
你有好看的衣服吗?
I don't see what's wrong with what I'm wearing.
我这件衣服有何不妥?
Sorry. I made a joke. I love your shoes.
说笑罢了  你的鞋不错
I don't know anything about banking.
我对银行业一窍不通
Oda Mae   would you just relax?
不知道这是否可行      放松一点
Listen   I'm nervous.
我很紧张
I'll get you through it.
我知道  但我会帮你
Your fake driver's license is great.
你的假驾照很好
Sam. I don't think I should do this.
森  我做不来的
Straight ahead. A stairway that says new accounts.
向前走  去开新户口的柜台
I ain't giving them money.
我不会给他们钱
Do what I say. Don't talk.
照我的话去做  别说话
Tell her you're here to fill out a signature card for a new account.
你说要为新帐户留签名样式
Can i help you?
有什么可以帮忙?
I'm here to fill out a signature card for a new account.
我想给新帐户留签名样式
Do you know your account number?
帐户号码是?
926...
926…
31043.
Rita Miller.  Who?
美拉      谁?
what?    Tell her Rita Miller.
什么?      说自己叫美拉
Rita Miller.
美拉
Rita Miller.Didn't you sign a card when you opened the account?
你开新帐户时没签名吗?
Carl Bruner opened it for you by phone
你打电话叫卡尔开的
and asked you to come in today.
他叫你来
Carl Bruner opened it for me by phone.
我打电话叫卡尔开的
Now he's asked me to come in today.
他叫我今天来补签      好
Is that right?  Yeah.
对吗?      对
All right. Just sign this card on the bottom line   please.
请在底线上签名
May I use your pen? Thank you so much.
我想借用你的笔  谢谢
No   no   no! Rita Miller.
不…签美拉的名字
I'm so sorry.
对不起
You know   I...I need another one. I signed the wrong name.
我签错了  请给我另一张
Make sure it goes up to the third floor file
叫她马上建档案
because you have a transaction to make.
你要进行交易
Make sure this goes to the third floor file.
请马上建立档案
I have a transfusion to make.
我要进行交易
A what?
什么?
Let's go.
走吧
You know what I mean. Can I keep this pen?
你明白的  我可以要这支笔吗?
yes   sure.
可以
Thank you so much.
谢谢你
Byebye.
再见
I just love these pens.
我很喜欢这些笔
What do you want to keep the pen for?
留着它干嘛?
Carl Bruner speaking.
我是卡尔
Hi   Carl.Mr. Balistrari.
卡尔      巴里塔利先生
Balistrari? Carl   it's me   John.John. John   sorry
什么?我是约翰      对不起
um   whatwhat whatwhat's up?
有什么事?
I've got the info on the Bradley portfolio.
我有毕莱的资料
right.I'll pick it up later all right?
知道了  我待会来拿
I'll be here till 6:00.
你可以在六时前来      好
I don't suppose I can talk you into losing the hat.
可以把帽子脱下吗?
You keep messing with me you'll be here by yourself.
你再说我就走
Shh. Now tell the guard you're here to see Lyle Ferguson.
告诉守卫  你要见佛格生
Hi. I'm here to see Lyle Ferguson   please.
我想见佛格生
Do you have an appointment?No   I'm here for my health.
有预约吗?      不  我没来意的
Tell him Rita Miller's here.
别那样说  告诉他美拉来了
YouYou just tell him Rita Miller's here.
你去告诉他美拉来了
One moment.
请等等
Don't embellish.  Jawoh.
别乱说话      别管我
Excuse me?
什么?
Now   listen. This guy Ferguson's a real jerk.
佛格生是个蠢蛋
I've known him for five years and he still thinks my name's
我认识他五年  他还以为我叫…
Why are you whispering?
你为何要细声说?
Just be quiet and listen.
安静点听我说
He's a social moron.Just tell the guard Ferguson knows you.
他很蠢的  你不用担心
You spent time with him and his wife Shirley
告诉守卫佛格生认识你
at the Brewsters' Christmas party last year. Got it?
你在去年的圣诞派对中
What is this in regards to?
跟他和他太太雪莉一起
What? He doesn't remember me?
请问有何贵干?
we spent all that time
他忘记我了吗?
at the Brewsters' Christmas party last year.
我和他夫妇一起参加圣诞派对
It was beautiful.
那里太漂亮了
A big old tree and thousands of presents everywhere.
当时的圣诞树很大  礼物又多
Gas.
胃气
I get a little gas from time to time.That's all. Gas.
我不时有胃气
Quit poking me!
别再碰我
Well   don't overdo it.
别做得过火
Now   listen. This'll be easy.Ferguson was so drunk
他当时醉了
he could've had a conversation with Tina Turner and not remember.
凡事记不起
I don't know   Sam.
会成功吗?
Here we go.
来了
Hello. Hello.Uh   yes.
你好
Of course yes.Well  it's been a...a long time.Long time.
很久没见      很久了
Ask how Bobby and Snooky are doing.
跟他问候波比和丝露琪
How are Bobby and Snooky doing?
波比和丝露琪好吗?
Fine. Fine. Thank you.
很好  有心
Uh   and how is your   uh   family?
Thank you for asking.
你的家人怎样?
couldn't be better.
好得不得了
Well...wonderful.
太好了
Tell him you've been wondering
问他证券的
how they did on the Gibraltar securities.
买卖如何
I was just wondering how did you do on the Gibraltar securities?
你买卖证券的情形如何?
The Gibraltar securities?
证券吗?
Well   it looks like we topped out on that one   huh?
看来赚了一些钱
Sure did.  Sure did.
当然了      当然了
That was a useful tip.
那内幕消息很不错
Good old Randy.Good old Randy.
兰狄真厉害      兰狄真厉害
Got a good old head on his shoulders.
这小子很有头脑
Her shoulders.Her shoulders.
这女子…
Randy.
兰狄
So   what   um...what brings you here today?
今天有何贵干?
You're closing an account.
结束帐户
I'm closing an account.
我来结束帐户
Do you have your account number?
你有帐户号码吗?
Yes?  Yes.
有?      有
926031043
92631043. Is that right?
926031043  对吧?
Well Rita it looks like you'll be withdrawing
你要在今天
$4 million from us today.
提取四百万吗?
$4 million!
四百万!
Say yes. Say yes!
说是的
Is that correct?
对吗?
Yes.
对      对
Yes. Yes   uh   yes!
对
Yes   that's correct.Easy   easy.
没错      别激动
Yes. Well   how would you like that?
想怎么拿走?
10s and 20s.     Pardon?
十元和二十元钞票   什么?
Tell him a cashier's check.
告诉他要银行本票
I think better a cashier's check.
银行本票比较好
A cashier's check. Fine.
好  本票
Well of course you know we require identification from everyone.
请出示身分证
I see.It's just procedural.
只是循例      我明白
Yes. I...Thank you.Well   I'll   uh   I'll be right back.
我很快回来
$4 million!
四百万!
Yeah   get me the First Island Bank of Nassau.It's on the Rolodex.
请接到拿素区第一岛银行
Well   we have some   uh   things for you to sign here.
你有些文件要签名
This officially closes the account.And here you are.
这会正式结束你的帐户
Now sign Rita Miller.
签美拉的名字
Rita Miller. That's my name.
美拉…是我的名字
My name. Rita Miller. My name.That's my name.
美拉是我的名字
Molly hi.Hi.Oda Mae I'll be right back.
请等等  我很快回来
Just anywhere?Right here.
随便签?      在这儿签名
Fine.
好
The check.This uhHere you are.
支票给你
Mama took the money that she made in the oil wells
妈要把油井赚来的钱
and she sunk it into gas pumps.
投资加油站
You know how they have at the gas station?
你知道她们干嘛投资加油站吧
It's very very lucrative.
相当赚钱
Oda Mae...it really adds up.
奥德美      真的赚很多…
We've have to go.Say goodbye.
我们要走了  跟他说再见吧
It's been a pleasure doing business with you.
我要走了  很高兴跟你有往来
Now   may I keep the pen?
我可以要这支笔吗?
Say good night to Bobby and Snooky for me.
替我问候波比与丝露琪
Byebye.Why are you rushing me?
为什么赶着走?
What is wrong?
有何不妥?
Excuse me. Lyle?
佛格生?
yes.     Molly.Molly.
是…      慕莉
Jensen. The woman you were just doing business with...
刚才离开的女人…
What did she want?
来做什么?
Did it have anything to do with Sam?
跟我和森有关的吗?
Sam? Why   no. No.
森?不
That was Oda Mae Brown   right?
她是奥德美吧?
No. Her name was Rita Miller.She was closing an account.
她叫美拉  来结束帐户的
Is there a problem?
有问题吗?
No   I guess not. Thank you.
没有  谢谢
Carl   is something wrong?
有什么问题?
Is somebody playing with the computers?What?
有人动过电脑吗?      什么?
One of my accounts is closed.
我有个帐户被终止了
Which account? What's wrong?You want me to call someone?
要通知其他人?
No   it's OK.I can do it. I got it.
不用了  我会处置
$4 million!What am I going to do with this money?
我该如何运用这四百万?
I'm going to buy the block.
我要买下大厦…不
I'm going to make my sister go to a fat farm.
我要买房子
I'm going to buy the building.
还要送我的姐妹去减肥中心
I've got an idea.
你想做什么?      我要买大厦
Please donate.
我有个主意
Take the check out of your purse.
什么主意?      把支票拿出来
Right. I should put it where nobody can get it.
对  要拿出来把它放好
No. No. Endorse it.
不  在背后签名
If I endorse it   then if I drop it
若丢了  拾到的人就可拿去兑现
somebody will get it.
这不是你的钱
I never said you were going to get the money.
我没说你可以拿这笔钱
It's blood money. I was killed for this money.
这笔钱累我丧命
Now endorse the check.
签名吧
What are you going to do with it?
你打算怎样处置它?
Look over there.To your left.
看看你的左边
You don't think I'm giving this $4 million
我不会把四百万块捐给修女
If you don't   they'll track you down.
你不这样做  他们就会找到你
to a bunch of nuns.Get rid of it.
你得摆脱这笔钱
Sam   you're killing me!It's $4 million!
是你要我的命  这是四百万
You'll go to heaven.
你会因此上天堂
I don't want to go to heaven.I want to cash the check.
我宁愿把支票拿去银行兑现
Hello.
你好
You'll thank me later.
你之后会多谢我
How are you doing?
你好吗?
Now   endorse it ""Rita Miller.""I know.
签美拉的名字      知道了
Make it out to St. Joseph's shelter.
收款人写
I can't believe you're making me do this.
想不到我会这样做
Now give it to her.
把支票给她
I want to feel it one more time.
我只是想多拿一会儿
Give the lady the check.I will!
把支票给她      我会
Hand her the check.You can do it.
你做得到的
Give her the check.I will!
给她      我会的了
Bless you   child. Bless you.
愿主保佑你
Give it to her.
把支票给她
Let go. Let go!
放手
Shit.
他妈的!
I'm proud of you   Oda Mae.
我以你为荣
I don't care. Stay away from me from now on.
我不在乎你是不是以我为荣
What is that nun going to do with it?
别再缠我  修女要这些钱干嘛?
Leave me alone. Never talk to me again.
又不能买东西  你别再跟我讲话
I think you're wonderful   Oda Mae.
你很了不起
Go ahead   search. You'll never find it.
继续找吧  你永远都找不到
They're going to kill you   Carl.
他们会取你的命
You and Willy.You're going to be fertilizer.
把你和威里杀死
They're going to bury you right next to Jimmy Hoffa.
把你们葬在大流氓的墓旁
Who's doing that?Who's doing that?
谁干的?
I thought we were having dinner.
你在哪儿?不是约好吃晚饭吗?
I know   Moll. I'm sorry.I just forgot.
对不起  我有点乱  我忘记了
Had trouble at the bank.
他在银行有麻烦
Forgot? I wish you'd called.I've been really worried.
你忘记了?我很担心你呢
Listen   Molly. I got to ask you about something.
我有些事情要问你
Yeah. He needs to borrow $4 million.
他想借四百万
When you said that you thought
你觉得
Sam was here that he was talking to you
森的鬼魂跟你说话
what did he say to you?
那种感觉是怎样的?他说什么?
What does that have to do with anything?
为什么这样问?
Just listen to me.
先听我的话
This psychic lady   I want to know what she told you.
那灵媒跟你说过什么?
Stop this.
放开我  停手
It doesn't matter. It wasn't real.
这不重要  因不是真的
What the hell happened to you tonight?
你今晚怎么了?
Does this have anything to do with her being at the bank today?
因为她今天到过银行?
The bank?Yeah. Ferguson said she closed an account.
银行?      佛格生说她结束帐户
Her name isn't even Oda Mae Brown.It's Rita Miller or something.
她不用奥德美的名字  而用美拉
Carl   are you all right?
你没事吧?
It's just my stomach. It's...
我的胃不舒服
Jesus.
天啊!
Do you have any like some PeptoBismol or something?Cyanide...
你有胃药吗?      给他砒霜吧
yeah. It's upstairs.Sit down. I'll get it.
你坐下  我去楼上拿给你
What's wrong?Does little Carl have a tummy ache?
怎么了?你胃痛吗?
What are you doing?
你想怎样对付我?
Now do you believe in ghosts?
你现在相信有鬼了?
I'll set the place on fire I swear to God.
我会放火烧这地方
I'll cut her throat.
我会杀死她
Carl.
卡尔
I swear to God. I'll cut her throat.
我说得出  做得到
I need that money and I want it tonight at 11 :00.
今晚11时前把钱还给我
If that psychic does not bring it here Molly is dead. OK?
灵媒不及时拿来  我就杀死慕莉
Carl   who are you talking to?
你跟谁说话?
Nothing. Now   Molly   listen to me.
没有  我要走了
I can't explain this now but there's a problem OK?
现在我不能解释
Something at the bank.
银行出了问题
Carl   you're scaring me.I'm sorry.
你吓倒我了      对不起
I'll come back about 11 :00.
我没空说  但我11时会回来
Why? Why not now?Molly look I'll come back.
为什么现在不说?      稍后再说
Like 11 :00   OK?
我11时再回来吧
Molly  but it's important. Got to go.
抱歉  但这事很重要  我要走了
Oda Mae!
11时见      奥德美
I'm Arsenio Hall.Don't try to adjust your television.I'm black.
请不要换台  我来也
I want to watch Love Connection.
我想换个频道
I love Love Connection.I love that man on there.That's Arsenio.
别转台  这是阿仙诺
So?You love Love Connection
你喜欢看
send your picture in there.
那就该寄张照片去
She did.
她已经寄了
They just haven't answered yet.
只是他们没回覆
Oda Mae?  Sam?
奥德美      森?
Not again.
别再来
They want the check   and they're coming for you.
他们来追索本票  你快走
The check you said they would never know about?
你不是说他们不会知道的吗?
Oda Mae   what's happening?
发生什么事?
Sam?
森?      他们来了  快走!
Get out of here!Now! Go!Put the damn remote down. Come on.
快走
Knock on the doors.
敲这道门
Help! Help!
救命
It's an emergency. Let us in.Who are you kidding?
让我们进去      你说笑吧?
Open up!
开门!
You can't come in.The cat don't like visitors.
你们不能进来  猫儿怕陌生人
She'll pee all over.
它会在沙发上撒尿…
They're going to get us.
他们会找到我们
Where's Sam?
森在哪儿?
The bitch just left.I'll check downstairs.
那婊子刚离开了      我去搜楼梯
Carl?
卡尔?
Willy!
威里
Hey   man. You got a serious problem   man.
你很有问题!
Help me!Help!
救命!
Willy!
威利
I heard the car. I was standing right there.
我听到车过来了 我就站在这
You could hear it across town.
你能听到它穿过城镇
That dude is dead.
那人死了
You're dead   Willy.
威里  你死了
No! No! No!
不
Help me!
救命
Tell the driver to hurry.
叫司机快一点
Yo   man   you want to step on it   please?
请开快一点
Lady   I'm driving as fast as I can.
我已经尽快了
Problems?
有问题吗?
Carl is that you?No. It's me Oda Mae. Listen.
卡尔  是你吗?      我是奥德美
Molly   I know what you think of me
我知道你怎样想我
but you are in serious danger.
我们必须一谈  你现在很危险
I got Sam here. We got to talk.
森也在这儿  我们想跟你谈谈
Get the hell out of here.
给我滚
I'm calling the police.
否则我报警
Tell her to do it.
叫她报警
Fine. We want you to call the police.
我们正想你报警
Let us in.  No.
让我们进来  不
Look   don't you get it?Sam wasn't just accidentally killed.
你还不明白?森的死不是意外
He was murdered.
是被人谋杀的
He found out Carl was laundering money at the bank.
他发现卡尔在银行替人洗黑钱
This guy Carl is dangerous.He tried to kill me.
卡尔是危险人物 他想杀了我
He's going to try to kill you too.
他也会杀了你的
You're in deep trouble.
你的处境很危险
Why are you doing this to me?Why are you doing this to me?
你为什么这样对我?
Why are you doing this to me?
你听到吗?你为什么这样对我?
I can't... I just can't...
我不可以…
Oda Mae. Oda Mae   tell her...tell her
奥德美 告诉她说
she's wearing the shirt that I spilled the margarita on
她身上的衬衫曾给我弄污
and the earrings I gave her for Christmas.
耳环是我送给她的圣诞礼物
Sam says you're wearing the shirt he spilled the margarita on
森说你身上的衬衫曾给他弄污
and the earrings he gave you for Christmas.
耳环是他送给你的圣诞礼物
Don't you see?I'm not a fake. Not about this.
你还不明白?我这次没骗人
Give me a penny.  What?
给我一个硬币      什么?
Push a penny under the door.
把硬币在门下推进去
Push a penny under the door?
你在说什么?
Do it.
照做吧
Tell her it's for luck.
说这是求好运
Sam says it's for luck.
森说这是求好运
We're between Green and Mercer on Prince.
这儿在格连和马西之间
The gray building across from the post office.
邮局对面的灰色大厦
Thanks   Sergeant.Please hurry.
警官  请快来
We'll be waiting.
我们等你
All right. They're on their way.Good.
他们快来了      好
So   what do we do now?Just wait.
现在怎办?      等着吧
Is Sam here?
森在吗?
Sam?
森?
I'm sitting beside her.
我坐在她身旁
He's sitting right beside you.
他坐在你身旁
Sam   can you feel me?
森  你感觉到我吗?
With all my heart.
全心全意
Says with all his heart.
他说全心全意
I'd give anything if I could just touch you once more.
我愿不惜一切去多接触你一次
He says he wishes he was alive again so he could touch you.
他说他想多接触你一次
Me   too.
我也是
OK. OK. Look.
好吧
You can use me.
你可以利用我
Use you?  You can use my body.
利用你?   上我的身
Use your body?Just do it quick before I change my mind.
上你的身?      在我改变主意前
Oh   my love
My darling
I've hungered for your touch
A long   lonely time
And time goes by
So slowly
And time can do so much
Are you still mine
I
Need your love
God speed your love
To me
Lonely rivers Flow
To the sea
To the open arms
Of the sea
Yeah
Oh   my love
My darling
I've hungered
Hungered for your...
Molly!Molly are you home?
慕莉?你在吗?
It's Carl.Fire escape.
是卡尔      太平梯
What's happening to me?
我怎么了?
Molly?
慕莉?
Molly!
Son of a bitch!
混蛋
Come on.
这边
Look. Look.
看
Let's go. Let's go.All right.
那边
Molly!
慕莉
Just get away from us   Carl.
别走近我们
Molly!
慕莉
You're just a liar.
你是个撒谎鬼
Listen to me. This woman's a thief.
她是个贼
She's a con artist.
是个骗子
Why are you doing this?Don't listen to her.
你为何这样做?      别相信她
Stop!
停下来
Just get away from us   Carl.I've called the police.
你快走  我已报警
Why are you doing this?
你为何这样做?
Don't interfere! She's a thief!
你别插手  她是个贼
All right. Give me the check.
把支票给我
Carl   no!Out of this   Molly!
不  别插手慕莉
Keep out of this   Molly!
别抓住我…
Get off of me!
放手
Where is it?
支票在哪?
Where is it?god damn it
支票在哪里?
I gave it away.
给了别人
You're lying.
你在说谎
Don't...lie to me   god damn it!
别骗我
The check.
把支票给我
Watch out Sam!I swear to God I'll kill her!
我会杀死她的
Now just...look.Just give me the check Sam OK?
把支票给我
I promise you I'll let her go if you just give it to me. OK?
若你给我支票  我就放了她
Sam?
森?
森
Carl.
卡尔
What?
什么?
Help!
救命
Are you two all right?
你俩没事吧?
Sam?
森?
Molly?
慕莉
I can hear you.
我听到你
God.
天啊!
Sam?They're waiting for you Sam.
森  他们在等你
I'll miss you.
我会想你的
Your mother would be proud.
你妈妈会很自豪
I'm going to miss you too Sam.You're all right.
我也会想你  你要保重
Bye   Oda Mae.
再见
Bye   Sam.
I love you   Molly.
我爱你
I've always loved you.
一直也爱你
Ditto.
我也是
It's amazing   Molly.
这很美妙
The love inside...you take it with you.
我们的爱至死不渝
See ya.
再见
Bye.